Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Eternal Joy With You= =Episode 23=
=الفرح الأبدي معك= =الحلقة 23=
Father.
أب.
Father!
أب!
Father, I know my mistake.
أبي، أنا أعرف خطأي.
I know my mistake.
أنا أعرف خطئي.
From now on, I will listen to everything you say.
من الآن فصاعدا، سأستمع إلى كل ما تقوله.
Father.
أب.
What are you thinking about?
ماذا تفكر فيه؟
The Prince suddenly committed suicide at this time.
وفي هذا الوقت انتحر الأمير فجأة .
I find it a bit strange.
أجد الأمر غريبًا بعض الشيء.
It's not strange that he died.
ليس غريبا أن يموت.
But the timing of his death was just right.
لكن توقيت وفاته كان مناسبا تماما.
You also think there's something suspicious about this.
وتعتقد أيضًا أن هناك شيئًا مريبًا حول هذا الأمر.
After all, we didn't see the scene.
بعد كل هذا، لم نرى المشهد.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
that Feng Zhengxin would die so easily?
أن فينج تشنغ شين سيموت بسهولة؟
Anyway, I don't believe it.
على أية حال، أنا لا أصدق ذلك.
What you hear may be false,
ما تسمعه قد يكون خاطئا،
but what you see is true.
لكن ما تراه هو الحقيقة.
Tomorrow, there will be a funeral.
غدا سيكون هناك جنازة.
Many people will definitely go to attend the funeral.
بالتأكيد سوف يذهب الكثير من الناس لحضور الجنازة.
I'm thinking
انا افكر
we could take this opportunity to go and find out the truth.
يمكننا أن نستغل هذه الفرصة للذهاب ومعرفة الحقيقة.
(Memorial)
(النصب التذكاري)
(Memorial Tablet of Prince Chong Feng Zhengxin)
(لوح تذكاري للأمير تشونغ فنغ تشنغ شين)
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
please accept my condolences.
أرجو أن تتقبل تعازيّ.
Do you come here
هل تأتي إلى هنا؟
to laugh at me?
لتضحك علي؟
That is not the case.
وهذا ليس هو الحال.
You misunderstand us.
لقد أسأتم فهمنا.
Xu Wanning,
شو وانينج,
do you know
هل تعلم؟
what I hate the most right now is seeing you
ما أكرهه أكثر الآن هو رؤيتك
with that smug, self-satisfied look.
مع تلك النظرة المغرورة والراضية عن نفسها.
You brought Pei Heng here today,
لقد أحضرت بي هينج إلى هنا اليوم،
just to tell me
فقط لتخبرني
that you are a winner
أنك فائز
and to see how miserable I've become because of you.
ولكي أرى كم أصبحت بائسًا بسببك.
Because of me?
بسببي؟
Xu Wanning,
شو وانينج,
everything I had was taken away by you.
لقد أخذت مني كل ما كان لدي.
My lover, my family.
حبيبتي وعائلتي.
Why?
لماذا؟
You are a scheming and flirtatious woman.
أنت امرأة ماكرة ومغازلة.
You always oppose me in everything.
أنت تعارضني دائمًا في كل شيء.
Everything I had was ruined by you. Why?
كل ما كان عندي دمر بسببك. لماذا؟
Because I can tell truth from lies;
لأنني أستطيع التمييز بين الحقيقة والكذب؛
I can distinguish good from evil;
أستطيع التمييز بين الخير والشر؛
I understand human nature;
أنا أفهم الطبيعة البشرية؛
I have never asked anything from others;
لم أطلب من الآخرين أي شيء أبدًا؛
I only trust myself;
أنا أثق بنفسي فقط؛
I don't believe in fate;
أنا لا أؤمن بالقدر؛
Everything I want, I fight for myself;
كل ما أريده، أقاتل من أجله بنفسي؛
I will take responsibility
سأتحمل المسؤولية
for the mistakes I made myself.
للأخطاء التي ارتكبتها بنفسي.
You bandit, bandit!
أيها اللص، أيها اللص!
You shameless person!
يا لك من شخص عديم الخجل!
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
ask yourself honestly.
اسأل نفسك بصراحة.
Which of your family members or loved ones
أي من أفراد عائلتك أو أحبائك
have I taken away?
هل أخذت بعيدا؟
You reap
انت تحصد
what you sow.
ما تزرعه
Now you have tasted this bitter fruit.
لقد تذوقت الآن هذه الفاكهة المرة.
Shouldn't you reflect
ألا يجب عليك أن تفكر؟
on what you have done?
على ما فعلت؟
Madman! You bunch of madmen!
مجنون! يا جماعة المجانين!
Someone! Drive them out!
أحد ما! طردهم!
I'd like to see who dares.
أريد أن أرى من يجرؤ.
If you don't take action today,
إذا لم تتخذ أي إجراء اليوم،
it will be you who die.
أنت الذي سوف يموت.
Do it!
افعلها!
Xiaoxiao, what are you doing?
شياوشياو، ماذا تفعل؟
Brother.
أخ.
Xiaoxiao,
شياوشياو،
my uncle's spirit in heaven
روح عمي في الجنة
also hopes to walk the final journey in peace.
ويأمل أيضًا أن يمشي في الرحلة النهائية بسلام.
Many thanks to you for being here.
شكرا جزيلا لك على تواجدك هنا.
The time has come.
لقد حان الوقت.
Let's get started.
دعونا نبدأ.
(Virtue and Diligence)
(الفضيلة والاجتهاد)
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
(Memorial Tablet of Prince Chong Feng Zhengxin)
(لوح تذكاري للأمير تشونغ فنغ تشنغ شين)
The incense is fine.
البخور جيد.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Ash.
رماد.
The ash is poisonous.
الرماد سام.
Xu Wanning, oh Xu Wanning,
شو وانينج، أوه شو وانينج،
you've finally fallen into my hands.
لقد وقعت أخيرا في يدي.
Yu've ruined my plans time and again.
لقد دمرت خططي مرارا وتكرارا.
Let's see how I torment you today.
دعونا نرى كيف أعذبك اليوم.
Uncle,
عم،
you… let her go.
أنت... دعها تذهب.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
All of your people have been under my control.
لقد كان جميع شعبك تحت سيطرتي.
What right do you have to negotiate terms with me?
ما هو الحق الذي لديك للتفاوض معي على الشروط؟
Nephew, it's a pity I didn't die, huh?
يا ابن أخي، من المؤسف أنني لم أمت، أليس كذلك؟
I thought you had met with disaster
اعتقدت أنك واجهت الكارثة
and I felt very sad.
وشعرت بحزن شديد.
Felt very sad?
هل شعرت بحزن شديد؟
Your act is quite convincing.
إن فعلك مقنع تماما.
I don't know why my brother chose you to be the Emperor.
لا أعلم لماذا اختارك أخي لتكون الإمبراطور.
You have no talent for governing the country.
ليس لديك الموهبة لحكم البلاد.
You are timid and cowardly by nature,
أنت خجول وجبان بطبيعتك،
clinging to life and afraid of death.
متشبث بالحياة وخائف من الموت.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
let me take your place and firmly hold this realm.
دعني آخذ مكانك وأمسك بهذه المملكة بقوة.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Uncle, you intend to kill me?
عمي هل تقصد قتلي؟
Kill you?
اقتلك؟
Kill you.
اقتلك.
Little nephew,
ابن أخي الصغير
have you forgotten this throne rightfully belongs to me?
هل نسيت أن هذا العرش هو من حقي؟
It was your father who snatched it from my hands.
لقد كان والدك هو الذي انتزعها من يدي.
For this very moment,
في هذه اللحظة بالذات،
I have waited for 30 years.
لقد انتظرت لمدة 30 عامًا.
30 years.
30 سنة.
Today, this funeral
اليوم هذه الجنازة
is prepared for all of you.
تم إعداده لجميعكم.
I will kill you.
سأقتلك.
Kill every single one of you.
اقتلو كل واحد منكم.
Make you accompany me in death for these 30 years.
أجعلك ترافقني في الموت لمدة 30 عامًا.
Jinlin Guards, where are you?
حراس جينلين، أين أنتم؟
How is that possible?
كيف ذلك ممكنا؟
The trap I set is flawless.
الفخ الذي وضعته لا تشوبه شائبة.
How could you possibly know?
كيف يمكنك أن تعرف ذلك؟
But Hongzhen Incense betrayed you.
لكن هونغزين إنسنس خانتك.
(Hongzhen Incense?)
(البخور هونغتشن؟)
When it reaches a certain concentration,
عندما يصل إلى تركيز معين،
it can make a person unconscious for three days,
يمكن أن يجعل الشخص فاقدًا للوعي لمدة ثلاثة أيام،
without a trace of life.
بدون أي أثر للحياة.
But it comes alive when it meets fire.
لكنها تنبض بالحياة عندما تلتقي بالنار.
You added oiled paper into this brazier.
لقد أضفت ورقًا مدهونًا بالزيت إلى هذا الموقد.
The flames will disperse the concentration of the Incense.
ستعمل النيران على تفريق تركيز البخور.
So when the time comes,
لذا عندما يحين الوقت،
you will wake up.
سوف تستيقظ.
But all the guests present will slowly be poisoned,
ولكن جميع الضيوف الحاضرين سوف يتم تسميمهم ببطء،
and gradually die.
ويموت تدريجيا.
Killing two birds with one stone.
قتل عصفورين بحجر واحد.
What a clever scheme!
ما هذه الخطة الذكية!
It was you who tampered with this room
لقد كنت أنت الذي تلاعب بهذه الغرفة
and saved everyone's lives.
وأنقذ حياة الجميع.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I applied medicine here in advance.
لقد تقدمت بطلب الطب هنا مسبقًا.
So everyone is not actually poisoned.
لذا فإن الجميع ليسوا مسمومين فعليا.
They just fell asleep for a short while.
لقد ناموا لفترة قصيرة فقط.
Now they should be about to wake up.
الآن ينبغي لهم أن يكونوا على وشك الاستيقاظ.
Xu Wanning, it's you again.
شو وانينج، أنت مرة أخرى.
Father.
أب.
I'll fight you to the end.
سأقاتلك حتى النهاية.
Do you know that the Emperor you've been protecting all along
هل تعلم أن الإمبراطور الذي كنت تحميه طوال الوقت
is actually the one who most wants you dead?
هو في الواقع الشخص الذي يريد موتك أكثر من أي شيء آخر؟
You are disabled because...
أنت معاق بسبب...
Uncle, go to the underworld
عمي اذهب إلى العالم السفلي
and accompany my father.
وأرافق والدي.
He must miss you very much.
لابد أنه سيفتقدك كثيرًا.
Father!
أب!
It's fake.
إنه مزيف.
It's all fake.
كل هذا مزيف.
Master.
يتقن.
What's wrong, Ruyi?
ما الأمر يا رويي؟
Master, Aunt Ning and Chang'an have left.
لقد غادر السيد والعمة نينغ وتشانجان.
They are gone.
لقد رحلوا.
What?
ماذا؟
They really left.
لقد غادروا حقا.
♪The old house's door remains tightly shut♪
♪ باب البيت القديم لا يزال مغلقا بإحكام ♪
♪Snow covers the stone table in front♪
♪الثلج يغطي الطاولة الحجرية في المقدمة♪
♪The you and I who once laughed♪
♪أنت وأنا الذين ضحكنا ذات يوم♪
♪Now only I am left alone♪
♪الآن أنا وحدي فقط♪
♪Snowflakes fall, blurring my sight♪
♪تتساقط رقاقات الثلج، مما يحجب بصري♪
♪As if trying to hide this farewell♪
♪كما لو كنت أحاول إخفاء هذا الوداع♪
♪Yet the pain feels so real♪
♪ومع ذلك فإن الألم يبدو حقيقيا جدا♪
♪Growing sharper in the snow♪
♪يزداد حدة في الثلج♪
♪Snow falls across the city, filling my heart♪
♪يتساقط الثلج في جميع أنحاء المدينة، ويملأ قلبي♪
♪The cold wind blows through a lonely corner♪
♪تهب الرياح الباردة عبر زاوية منعزلة♪
♪Jade fragments drift in the wandering snow♪
♪شظايا اليشم تنجرف في الثلج المتجول♪
♪My heart sinks into the vast frozen river♪
♪يغرق قلبي في النهر المتجمد الواسع♪
♪Time wears on as snow falls again and again♪
♪يمضي الوقت بينما يتساقط الثلج مرارًا وتكرارًا♪
♪Just like your endless heartlessness♪
♪تمامًا مثل قسوة قلبك التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪Frosted branches shake off stardust♪
♪الأغصان المتجمدة تتخلص من غبار النجوم♪
♪It's my endless devotion to you♪
♪إنه إخلاصي اللامتناهي لك♪
♪Snow falls across the city, filling my heart♪
♪يتساقط الثلج في جميع أنحاء المدينة، ويملأ قلبي♪
♪That pure white is an endless longing♪
♪هذا اللون الأبيض النقي هو شوق لا ينتهي♪
♪The wind can't scatter the snow it piles into a cocoon♪
♪لا تستطيع الرياح أن تبعثر الثلوج التي تراكمها في شرنقة♪
♪Trapping me in this winter♪
♪حاصرني في هذا الشتاء♪
♪Snow fills the city, drifting toward the horizon♪
♪الثلوج تملأ المدينة، وتنجرف نحو الأفق♪
♪Carrying away the sorrow of farewells♪
♪حمل حزن الوداع بعيدًا♪
♪I linger alone in the snow♪
♪أنا أبقى وحدي في الثلج♪
♪Waiting for a fate that will never come♪
♪في انتظار مصير لن يأتي أبدًا♪